

HAMEES MJM

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I am the self motivated and energetic individual, who tries to get a challenging and competitive position in the IT industry, to contribute my knowledge, skills and my experience for a part of the success of the organization. With the experience of my past works, I'm capable to work well under the pressure. I would welcome the opportunity to discuss my suitability in more detail.

CONTACT

Social Media:



in /in/hamees-mjm-a38b5a129/

Address:

297, Makkamady Road, Maruthamunai-03

Phone:

+94 75 23 88 697

Email:

hamees1993@gmail.com

LANGUAGE

English, Tamil & Sinhala

REFERENCE

MR. R.K. AHAMED RIFALKARIAPPER

Senior Lecturer ICT. Facuty of Technology, SEUSL Phone: +94 76 1313 778 Email: rk@seu.ac.lk

MR. M.S. SUHAIL RAZEETH

Lecturer ICT. Facuty of Applied Science, UWUSL Phone: +94 75 4571 535 Email: suhail@uwu.ac.lk

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Hons in Computing & Information Systems

Sabaragamuwa University of Sri Lanka, Belihuloya.

Advanced Level - Physics-B, Combined Maths-C, Chemistry-C Km/Km/Al-manar central college, Maruthamunai

PROJECTS

- Medical Clinic Management System for university Mini Project (PHP)
- E-commrece Textile Website (Wordpress) citywalk.lk
- Sports Academy Website (Codeigniter) asspek.lk
- Phone Specifications Website (Codeigniter) phonespex.com
- Digital Consultancy Website (React JS) mjsoft.lk
- Portfolio Website (React JS) hamees.mjsoft.lk
- Classified Advertising Website (React JS) adsin.lk

EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2022

Full Stack Engineer - CYBER ACTIONS, Maruthamunai, Sri Lanka

Developed the frontend & backend infrastructure for projects.

- Crypto Currency Related Financial Investment Website.
- Wordpress Based Ecommerce Website.
- Worked with API s to integrate payment gateway for Perfect Money and USDT digital currencies.

Used Technologies:

PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, Bootstrap, MySQL, WordPress

2022 - Present

Full Stack Engineer - ALPHA HEALTH GROUP, Maruthamunai, Sri Lanka

Developed the frontend & backend infrastructure for projects.

- Career Portal Website.
- Online Medical Consultancy website

Used Technologies:

PHP, Codeigniter, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, Bootstrap, MySQL,

2022 - Present

Founder & CEO - adsin.lk, Maruthamunai, Sri Lanka

Established a Classified Advertising Agency.

- Designed & Developed a website as a full stack developer.
- Google Adsense, Google Analytics and Digital Marketing.

Used Technologies:

React JS, PHP, HTML, SCSS, JavaScript, NPM, JSX, MySQL

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

HTMI CSS/SCSS **JAVASCRIPT WORDPRESS JQUERY REACT JS NPM PHP CODEIGNITER LARAVEL MYSOL PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR VSCODE GITHUB NEXT JS**